(upbeat music)
- Hello everybody, and welcome to another episode
of Little Fish.
My name's Andrew Hunter Murray,
and joining me at The Fact Table
to dish out some of your brilliant facts
that you've been sending in.
Uh, uh, James Harkin and Dan Treiber.
- Hey Andy.
- Hello Andy.
You've come for, I'm just painting a picture
for those who are listening and not watching.
You've come sort of dressed as each other today.
- We've got black t-shirt.
Oh, I've got a black shirt on.
You've got a black polo.
- Yep.
- And have you got shorts on?
- I got blue trousers on and James has a beige shorts.
- But in fairness Andy is just imagining
what's happening under the table.
- I certainly am.
- Don't look under there.
- Stop what it wants.
We've got to show you a record.
Right, um, has anyone got a fact?
- This comes in from Eric Nosborn.
Eric Nosborn says, "Hi.
Since you're going to my hometown of Lund,
I thought I'd send in one of my favorite Lund facts.
We are going to Lund very soon.
We're going to be--
Since Sweden, we are playing the festival there
and we're going to be doing a live podcast recording.
So, uh, come along if you're in the area.
This is the fact that Eric has sent.
- I think it sold out.
- Wow, come stand outside the doors.
- Kind of cool viral marketing,
but with no purpose.
Now it's sold out.
Clevverly done, but no point.
- To no point.
They might move us into a bigger room.
- That'd be good.
- That'd be great.
- Right in for a bigger room.
Uh, here we go.
Can I get to the email?
(laughs)
This is from Eric.
He says, "The discovery that humans
have 46 chromosomes was made at Lund University."
- Ooh.
- "Before that, for over three decades,
we thought humans had 48 chromosomes,
and I guess no one bothered to double-check."
They add in brackets.
It's a bit more complicated than no one bothered
to double-check, but that sounds funnier.
So--
- Well, we knew that chromosomes existed.
- Yep.
- And then it turned out that two of them didn't count.
- Exactly.
- And the point of the email from Eric is that
additionally Lund has the area phone code of 46.
And Sweden has a national phone code of 46.
So humans had actually had 48 chromosomes after all.
The discovery would have been made in Poland instead.
(laughs)
- Is that how that works?
- Yeah.
- That's brilliant.
- Okay.
- Wonderful.
- If we lose it tomorrow, it'll be in the UK.
- Yes.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
(laughs)
- It's coming.
It's coming.
(laughs)
- Chroma's gonna come in, hope.
- Yeah, I love those area code facts.
And I did try to find a few.
I was reminded of one that we actually did
as a headline many years ago,
which is that the telephone code for Cape Canaveral
where they launch all the rocket ships is three, two, one.
Beautiful.
- I've got facts here.
- Yeah.
- This is from Rachel Cunning.
And Rachel Cunning has fact number one
that she entitles its two liqueurs and a cocktail.
And this is about the current World Cup,
which I think is still ongoing when this goes out.
Certainly England probably still have it in mind.
(laughs)
We've just beaten the Democratic Republic of Congo
the day before we recorded this.
But this is about someone who's already gone out Curacao.
Curacao, who is the smallest country
to ever qualify for the World Cup.
They are currently managed by Dick Advocate.
And they have a player called Jill Magarita.
One team, three drinks.
- Lovely.
- Curacao, Advocate and Magarita.
- And all very much from the fun end
of the cocktail spectrum, I'd say.
- Do you think Advocate is really fun?
- What was the favor of Advocate?
- Is it?
- It's not Advocate.
- It's not Advocate, it's lawyers.
- I'm gonna Google it.
It's made from egg yolks, sugar, brandy and vanilla.
- That's quite fun.
- That's fun.
- I suppose so.
- These are big snowballs.
- Yeah.
- It's not like boring old Sherry.
- No.
- They don't have a player called Newcastle Brownale
or anything.
(laughs)
- I think that's a brilliant fact.
- Lovely.
- Yeah, Rachel says, I'm sure James already knew them.
I did know about the Curacao and Advocate thing,
but I didn't know about Jill Magarita.
I'd never heard of them until the World Cup started.
So that's really good.
- Brilliant.
- Have you ever had Curacao?
It's like blue.
- I have a blue Curacao.
- Blue balls.
- Blue balls, named after a guy called Balls.
- Really?
- Yeah, you probably wouldn't think it was named after
the medical condition of having very big testicles.
- I don't know what, is this a drink?
- A blue ball.
- Blue balls, it's the brand name of Curacao.
- I don't know that.
- I think.
- Yeah, or Balls Blue maybe.
- Okay.
- You call it Balls Blue.
But yeah, Curacao, do you know what it was invented?
- The Netherlands.
- Yeah, in Flanders, of course, maybe on Belgium, just about.
But yeah, because, so in Belgium, as opposed to the Netherlands,
but because Curacao is a Dutch colony,
they could get the oranges from Curacao.
They're really better, and you don't really want to eat them,
but the orange skin is really nice if you boil it down
with alcohol, and that's what they make it out of.
- Oh, that's great.
- That is good.
- That's really good.
Oh, that's a lovely fact.
I have a World Cup fact.
- Oh, cool.
- This comes in from Adam Rodriguez.
His fact is, the soccer balls currently in use for the World Cup
must be charged before each match.
- Yeah.
- Charged.
- It's got to charge them.
- They have a chip in them, and so you can tell
if the ball's gone over the line.
- Oh, to help with the various technical mumbo jumbo
that you have to do these days.
- That's very interesting.
Can I just quickly add to that point?
'Cause there was a match on that just went with England,
Diocongo, and the commentators on the BBC
kept sort of bringing up this thing
that almost sounded like a conspiracy theory.
They were saying they keep swapping the balls.
Why do they keep swapping the balls?
And they were reminded of deflate gates in America
in the NFL.
- So deflate gate was where Tom Brady was using balls
that were slightly flatter, 'cause it made them easier
to throw and catch.
- Why did they call that deflate gate
and not the Brady crunch?
- Yeah. - 'Cause they didn't have you.
- Yeah.
- But there is a thing, there is a thing about these balls,
which is controversial.
- Yeah, they've used a fly in a weird way.
- They've used a new design.
I think it's four panels on the ball.
Basically, at a certain speed, it undergoes drag crisis
and it moves faster.
It speeds up, and it's because the air around it
goes into a turbulent state,
and that disrupts the drag on the ball.
So suddenly, if you kick it fast enough, it then speeds up.
And a lot of the goalies are saying,
"That was a lot faster than I thought it was gonna be."
How mad is that?
- That's wild.
- And you know what, time of recording
were about to play Mexico next,
and because of that altitude difference there,
and the air's a lot thinner, apparently it's even worse
when you go and play an altitude.
- Really? - Yeah.
- I think that's a good conspiracy theory
that you know the ball, 'cause it's got a chip in it
and people are going to say, "Oh, it's actually a drone."
- Yes. - And the whole thing's been controlled
by Big Football too.
- It's a spy. - It's a spy.
- I like it.
- I feel like the outcome's been fixed.
- I feel like it would be obvious
if someone kicked the ball and suddenly it started flying
and then turned left and then turned right,
and then got shot down by a Ukrainian soldier.
- I know, yeah, I feel like, yeah, yeah.
- But there's, well, it's not that thing.
- I had, 'cause it would just never become a fact,
unless I say it, a fact that was not picked
for an upcoming fish episode.
But I just really like it, which is that Cristiano Ronaldo
is one of three players ever to score a goal
in every minute of a football game.
- She was a good game, wasn't it?
(laughing)
- What about during half time?
- You have a score to goal during half time?
- No.
- He's not that good, is he?
- Great, well, that's a really good fact.
- Let's have another.
- Yeah, let's have another.
Here is one from Waleed Malik, who says,
"I'm writing to share a couple of Canadian late names
I discovered recently.
"I know you discussed Canadian lakes on the podcast before,
"but I don't think these came up.
"There is a lake in British Columbia called another lake."
- Oh, yeah.
- Just called another lake.
It was really nice.
There's right next to another lake.
There was a second lake that is called
and another lake.
(laughing)
- I can say that was in my notes for that episode.
- It wasn't ever about saying it.
- And I checked on Google Maps to make sure
they definitely existed and they do.
- Fantastic.
- Yeah.
- It was originally proposed, but the notes on it,
this is in 1968 say, "This is not a satisfactory name
"and it won't be used on BC Topo Maps,"
so it's the official maps.
However, because a longstanding usage just happened,
it just buckled, but it did get a rejection
and it overrided it for fun.
- It's confusing though,
if you're bringing the emergency services
and you're saying help, I've fallen into another lake.
That is confusing.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Another lake.
(laughing)
- Oh, that's good.
That's very good.
- Very nice.
- Here is a fact from Lin Juliana Soviknis.
You tell us about Jigsaws and that it is impossible
to make a square puzzle with exactly 1,000 pieces.
So all of them have more than 1,000 pieces.
Now, first of all, we're talking rectangles, not squares.
- Sure.
- Okay, so the idea is your Jigsaw,
the image of it has to be on the box, okay?
And so that has to be roughly the same shape
as an A4 piece of paper.
- Yes.
- 'Cause that's how big they make the boxes.
You can make different sized boxes.
You have to go to a specialist box making place to do that.
If you want a run of the mill games box from off the shelf,
you're gonna get an A4 size.
- And the problem is actually with big box,
as opposed to with big Jigsaw, right?
- Yeah, and big maths,
because if you want an exact A4 sized Jigsaw,
the side of a A4 piece of paper divided by the width,
is a square root of two.
So you need to come up with two numbers
that approximately, when you get one of them,
and you divide it by the square root of two,
you get the other one.
- That's impossible, 'cause it's an irrational number.
But the closest they can get, usually,
is 38 by 27, which is 1026 pieces.
So most 1000 piece Jigsaws have 1026 pieces.
- That's so annoying.
- Now, we were gonna do this on QI last year,
'cause I read this fact as well,
and I was gonna give Alan Davis a big box
with 1000 piece Jigsaw, and say,
how many pieces are in that Jigsaw?
And the hilarity was gonna win shoe.
But then Mike Turner, who's one of the researchers
who does puzzles, had a look at the Jigsaw,
he was making at the time,
and found out that it did have 1,000 pieces.
- Oh no.
- So I do believe that what Lin said is true
for many Jigsaws.
If you look at the internet,
they definitely agree, like people have checked.
But there are definitely some.
The one that Mike was doing was made by a company
called Gibson's, who are a proper Jigsaw company.
And so there are some that have exactly 1,000 pieces now.
- Well, 20 by 50 is 1,000.
So if you just had a slightly longer thing,
they need to have to buy a slightly longer box.
- No, I know, I know.
I'm gonna talk to the box people later.
I just don't think of them as.
- No, like it is possible to multiply two numbers
together to get 1,000,
but then the standard box sizes means
that the image on the box wouldn't look
like the thing you were making.
- That's why my innovation
of a fold-out poster of the thing,
you don't get a picture on the box.
- Well, you do get those in kids' ones, yeah.
- Also, here's a great idea.
- I'm sure it will be a 1,000 by 1 Jigsaw.
- Yeah.
- That sounds hard.
That's a real challenge.
- It depends if each have a number on them.
It's quite easy.
(laughing)
But if it's just an image of a snake,
it might be quite tricky.
- It's a snake.
(laughing)
- Well, I've got the A-N-S-P, so I know where that goes.
Well, I've got the head, so I know where that goes.
(laughing)
- That's a great start.
- Great news.
This one has two edges.
It's so useful.
(laughing)
So he's saying that no matter how lucrative
and the amount of money a Jigsaw company is making,
they're held back from innovation by the box companies.
- I don't really know how it is.
- It seems like it.
It does seem like big boxes got them by the dots.
- Wow.
- I used to know someone who ran a couple of books.
- Actually, really easy.
- He really surprised me.
- He surprised me.
(laughing)
- He doesn't invite you to add that he barks
because you're a bit worried.
(laughing)
- What can you tell us?
- It doesn't go any further than that.
(laughing)
- That's it.
- My friend's dad used to make the boxes for Stanley Kubrick.
- You see, this is an anecdote Sunday.
(laughing)
- He was upset with box sizes.
And so Kubrick designed his own boxes.
John Ronson did a whole thing about this.
- Yeah, he went and saw the archive.
John Ronson was looking through all the boxes
of Stanley Kubrick's archives,
but then he was going, these boxes look very different.
And it's because he designed these boxes
and my friend's dad.
- John Ronson doesn't have any stories like that.
- I don't know, none of these told me.
That's it really throws into relief how bad my one was
when Dan comes up with a Stanley Kubrick cardboard box,
personal anecdote.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
- I can imagine you and he were about to go,
I'm going to tell this story, no one's going to top this.
(laughing)
(upbeat music)
- Can I do another fact?
- Yeah, you go.
- Okay, this is a fact from Shane Carroll,
and it's about a chess move called The Greek Gift, okay?
And that's where you lay a trap for your opponent.
You sacrifice a bishop.
- If you're a slave, you should sacrifice the horse.
- What a good point.
But basically you sacrifice a bishop
and you lure your opponent's king into a dangerous position,
and then you can clobber the king
and you'll checkmate that way.
So, Greek gift horse.
That's why it's named that, right?
- Maybe.
- Maybe. - Oh no.
(laughing)
- Oh, damn it.
- But according to the Oxford Companion to chess,
this is named after Joe Gino Greco,
a 17th century player who frequently used it.
- Now, where did he get his name?
- Because El Greco, the painter,
was had Greek heritage, I'm sure.
- Interesting, interesting.
Well, Greco was from Italy, that's correct.
(laughing)
So, it could be this.
It could also be that it's a Greek gift named after that.
When you get that far back,
the etymology is a bit hairy.
But Shane, I just want to say thank you
for keeping it alive.
- Very nice. - Very nice.
- Do you think there might be more squares
on a chess board if the boxes were allowed
to be a bit bigger? (laughing)
- Very nice.
- So, here's something from Lynn Lim,
who has PhD in immunology and is writing from Switzerland.
And this is about a way of administering vaccines
intranasally where the mucus inside your nose
then is able to attack the pathogens.
- Okay. - Whatever you've got.
But the amazing thing is that the mucus
in the rest of your body then can also attack the pathogens.
And what that means is that you can give someone a vaccine
of the nose and protect them from infections in the vagina.
- Brilliant. - Wow.
- And vice versa?
- Well, they're currently working on that.
- Okay.
- This is called common mucusal immunity.
It's quite, I've looked at a couple of papers.
It's quite trendy at the moment in immunology.
But yeah, they're working out whether you'll be able
to do it the other way, do a passery up there.
And then it will stop you from getting occult.
- Wow. - Wow.
Isn't that amazing? - That is incredible.
- That's really good. - And one reason it's quite good
is because using the suppository or the passery
sometimes can help the medicine get a bit slower
into your body.
If you do a nose spray, it just goes straight up there.
Whereas the other ones kind of dissolve a little bit.
So if you need to release the active ingredient
a bit slower, then putting it up your nanny might help.
- They're both going straight up there, I suppose.
- Yeah, I suppose. - Yeah.
- You're nanny. - You're nanny.
- You're nanny, yeah.
- That's a-- - It's a Sarah Millican thing.
- Yeah, it is. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I mean, all women have them both.
(laughing)
- She's not a copy right in.
- Sorry, Sarah.
- Oh, dear. - Wow.
- And that crossbow number's Lynn Lynn.
- Lynn Lynn. - Brilliant name as well.
- Yeah. - Right.
That's enough of your facts.
Now it's time for some of our facts.
Because if you join Club Fish, our private members club,
by going to patreon.com/clubfish,
if you join at the friend of the podcast here,
then you will get a certificate
and custodianship of one of our headline facts
from the last 12 glorious years of podcasting.
So let's dish out a few of those now.
Who would like to dish one out?
- I'll go first. - Okay.
- This one now goes out to Awain Wilson
and Awain, your fact is that every time Alfred Hitchcock
had a cup of tea, he always smashed the tea cup.
- He was so focused on his stuff.
He probably didn't even notice
that he was smashing the tea cup, you know?
Oh, I thought he was doing it to make a point.
I just feel like that feels more Hitchcockian to me
that he would just be like, get that out of here.
I'm ready to go for a next bit.
- Psycho. - He was a bit alone, yeah.
- Lovely, lovely.
Well, at the time, I think we set up a straw mind
to myself of the fragility of human life.
- Which feels like an actual psycho thing.
- Sorry, I pushed you in the face to remind myself
of the fragility of human life.
- Also how many cups did it?
'Cause I have six or seven cups of tea a day, right?
So I would, I would before long have a room full of shards.
- Yeah.
- As in, there must be a Hitchcock pyramid somewhere,
which is just full of all of his uprochery.
- Yeah, it's surprising that they won't collect it
and sold off as little bits of, 'cause remember,
I mean, who wouldn't want to buy that?
- I absolutely would buy that.
- I know you would.
- The dentist who was associated with Winston Churchill,
remember, he used to throw his teeth at the wall.
And I believe it was him who used to collect all the cigar butts
that were dropped on the floor
and he would give them his presents
and sell them off and so on.
These little things are great.
- No, absolutely, yeah.
- Mylene class used to give away the Pope's toilet paper.
- Do you remember that?
- Yeah.
- I'm just saying there's an industry, Hitchcock.
- Alfred Hitchcock.
- Very good.
I mean, it doesn't have anything to do with what that's just
being saying.
He's really nice.
- Well, I think you just cut from the fact to that, can't you?
- I was just padding, so you could think of a joke.
I was just helping.
- Well, it worked.
- Yeah, yeah, right.
Let's have another one, then.
- Okay, this goes to John Riley.
And the fact is, Lord Byron's nickname for William Wordsworth
was William Turd'sworth.
- Great fact.
- I love that fact.
- You're a big fan of Byron.
- I am.
- He's your family.
- Yeah, he's a funny writer.
- Naughty boy, but a funny poet.
- Yeah.
- And there aren't many of those around, God knows.
- I like to think that you are the Lord Byron
of the Fish Podcast, and I'm the William Wordsworth
because I, you know, lived in the Lake District
and--
- Yeah, because I've an exhausting nickname for you.
- Yep.
(laughing)
- You're a shag machine, Andy.
- Yeah.
- You're gonna die young.
(laughing)
- I spend a little bit too much time with my sister.
- Oh, dear.
So there we go.
That's a great fact.
I'll dish one out.
- Yeah.
- To Douglas Ingram.
And your fact, Lucky You Douglas is that
replacement eyelids can be made from foreskins.
So if you've, you know, had an accident
and you need an, you know, an eyelid substitution,
that sounds very, very fragile skin there.
You can make it out of a foreskin.
- Yeah.
- Probably got a few eyelids out of one foreskin.
- I would have thought.
- Or it would be one very floppy eyelid.
- Yeah, you'd try that.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Can you do it the other way around
if you regret your circumcision?
Can you get your eyelids put on your foreskin?
- You'd love very surprised all the time
with you.
- Well, you'd be feeling it.
- Yeah, yeah, I imagine.
- Oh, dear.
So yeah, but there you go.
Thin skin.
Very useful. - Very useful.
- Okay, here is a fact now.
Under the custodial ship of Karai Lorrentay
and Karai, your fact is that the first item
to be sent by a New York's pneumatic tube postal system
was an artificial peach.
And the second was a live cat.
(laughing)
- I didn't think at the time.
- What use is there for an artificial peach?
- I suppose it's not gonna bruise.
- Good point, but then it's not a good test, is it?
I mean, the cat will bruise.
- You need to know.
- The person who managed to persuade,
let's say, the cat's to go into that tube.
The cat's like going into small spaces sometimes though, don't they?
- Yes, but they will do it under their own rules.
- Yeah, of sure.
- Yeah, that's fair.
- Like if you try and put them into a small space,
they will have absolutely none of it.
- Right, okay.
- Like, can we wanna put our cat into her little box
to take her to the vet or something?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I love a pneumatic tube.
- I knew you weren't.
(laughing)
- Your favorite pneumatic tube?
- Oh, don't, don't, 'cause we'll be here hours.
(laughing)
- All right, shall I bug another one in here?
- This is for Georgina Pereira.
And your fact is, scientists have invented algae
that tastes like bacon.
- Brilliant.
- Faken.
- I mean, it exists, right?
- Yeah.
- What do they make that stuff out of?
- I have had quite a bit of artificial bacon in my time.
- Yeah, sure.
- Sorry, Dan probably knows now
about how Charlie Chaplin's grandson
and who he knows is made of fake bacon, whatever, I don't care.
But I would say one of the problems with a lot of the fake bacon
is that fake bacon is quite hard to do really well.
And some of the stuff I've had has tasted like fish.
- Really?
- Yeah, you get it.
And it's just got that little tang of fishiness.
So maybe I've had algae based stuff, I don't know.
- Oh, I see, maybe.
- It's possible.
- Yeah.
- That's very good.
- Corn, can you get corn?
Bacon.
- Corn.
- We're in New Jersey, so yeah, why not?
- Yeah.
- You can add bacon, taste to corn.
Just like you can add any taste to corn.
Corn is named after a hunt.
- Is it?
- Yeah, the corn is a famous hunt in the countryside.
- And then there was like a big mansion or something.
I'm gonna say that has the same name as this corn.
And then they named it after that area, I think.
- 'Cause you'd think it would be 'cause it's related to corn.
It was absolutely not, it's bizarre.
- Very good.
- It won't be on the front page of your new book.
- What?
- All of the things that are named for a slightly different reason.
- No.
'Cause it's not named after a Mr. Tony Corn.
(laughing)
It's a problem.
- It'll be an appendix.
- Those have another one.
This one is going out to Brian Wood.
Brian, your fact is that telescopes have a new telescope smell
that can break them.
- Wow.
- That's very cool.
- This is about off-gassing.
It's like when you have a new car, there's a new car smell.
And it's 'cause all the chemicals are kind of settling down.
And it turns out telescopes are exactly the same.
- And then didn't cars like add it artificially?
Once they stopped having these sort of weird chemicals
that came off thing.
- Most people kind of liked it.
So they started putting sprays of fake car smell in there.
- I love the smell.
- Do you?
- The last time you got a new car every week, isn't it?
(laughing)
- So there you go, that's your fake Brian.
Hope you like it.
- Very nice.
Have we got time for one or two more?
- Go on, let's have one.
- Okay.
This one now is under the custodianship of Zrax Z-R-A-A-X.
You don't need me to tell you how to spell your name Zrax.
I'm sure you've had to do it to people who run hotels
almost every year of your life.
But your fact is now that there is a museum in North Korea
that has a scaled down replica of the world's largest table.
- I would have bet.
All my money that that was an anti-facts,
and I could see it was mine.
- Ah, how interesting.
I think the world's largest table was used
in some kind of diplomatic thing.
- Oh really?
- And the replica was because it's a replica of that incident.
But still, it just looks like a novel size table.
- Oh, such a good thing.
- It's wonderful.
It's absolutely wonderful.
Yes, James, you're so right.
It was a present given to North Korea
by another country for their national friendship exhibition.
- Oh, I hope they sell it in the gift shop as well.
Just a little key ring size.
World's biggest table.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's great merch.
- It's so simple.
- I mean, when they sent it over,
I wonder who made the box.
- All right, why don't we give one more?
One last fact, and this is for Keith Lovett,
as part of the preparation for the D-Day landings,
the Allies used condoms to collect soil and sand
from the Normandy beaches.
- Very nice.
Presumably so that you can know
what constitutes the sand,
and it's not gonna be too sandy or too hard or whatever, is it?
- You basically, yeah.
- I could have, again, with a gun to my head,
I know what I said, this was one of my facts,
but it was anus, and...
- It was incredibly dangerous, wasn't it,
as in they had to go and get close up
to an occupied enemy beach, get some sand,
and then go back and they were in midget submarines, I think.
- And do you think they got caught?
- They would just show the condom and say,
"No, I'm a pervert."
(laughing)
"Ah, yes, that's fine, Keith.
Go back, go back."
- Almost certainly, yeah.
- Well, there you go, Keith, that's your fact.
- What a mission to be given.
- We'd like you to go and see how dangerous the place
that we're gonna go is.
- Yeah.
- You'll go largely on your own, that's amazing.
- It's all that we're gonna send you to Germany
for a top secret mission.
Oh, wow, yeah.
We're gonna send you with 500 condoms.
(laughing)
- Wow, this sounds amazing.
- I thought when you said I'd have protection,
you meant guns, what's this?
- Oh, well, there you go, Keith, that's your fact.
Congratulations to all of our new custodians.
That is, of course, Keith, Zrax, Brian,
Georgina, Karoy, Douglas, John, and Owen.
Hope you love them.
If you would like your own fact, please just go to patreon.com/clubfish
and join Clubfish and we'll do the rest.
But until then, we'll be back with another episode
of Little Fish in a week, another episode of Big Fish
in four days, another episode of Drop us Alive,
potentially in either two days or nine days,
depending on your membership status
and your availability.
You don't have to listen on the day of release.
- Keep going, Andy.
You can do it.
Just look, look, in the distance,
you can see it.
The word goodbye.
You can see it there, just walked towards it.
(laughing)
Anya.
Come on, Andy.
- Andy, final thoughts, dad and James.
- Send it.
- Good, goodbye.
(upbeat music)